Raoul family papers, 1865-1985
Emory University
- Letters and personal papers, 1865-1982, Series 1; Boxes 1-35, OP 1-2
  - Eleonore Raoul papers, 1894-1982, Subseries 1.12; Personal name.; Boxes 30-34; OP 1-2
    - Suffrage papers, 1915-1920
    - Suffrage correspondence, 1915-1920 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Equal Suffrage Party of Georgia - Members' checklists, 1915 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous materials re suffrage movement in Georgia (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - "Woman's Journal and Suffrage News Traveling Kampaign Kit" (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Suffrage schools, 1913-1916 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Suffrage - Printed materials (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Suffrage - Clippings (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Suffrage - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - The International Woman Suffrage News, 1917, 1919 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - The Suffragist, 1917, 1918, 1919 (Box 33, Folder 10-12)
    - The Woman Citizen, 1918 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Woman's Journal and Suffrage News, 1915-1916 (Box OP1)
    - The Woman Voter, 1915 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - "Vote for Women's Suffrage," November 2, 1915 [preservation copy of poster in OP2a] [Image 0548-002.tif] (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Suffrage posters (Box OP2)
    - Suffrage poster, "Vote for Women's Suffrage," November 2, 1915 [RESTRICTED, see Box 33, folder 15 for preservation copy] (Box OP2a)
    - League of Women Voters papers, 1922-1959
    - Atlanta League of Women Voters - Correspondence, 1922-1944 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Atlanta League of Women Voters - Atlanta Plan Charter Campaign, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Atlanta League of Women Voters - Treasurer's records, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
    - Atlanta League of Women Voters - The New Citizen, 1922, May (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Atlanta League of Women Voters - Printed materials, 1922-1959 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Atlanta League of Women Voters - Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - DeKalb County League of Women Voters - Finance drive, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - DeKalb County League of Women Voters - Miscellaneous, 1946-1959 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - League of Women Voters of Georgia - Correspondence, 1946-1948 (Box 34, Folder 10-11)
    - League of Women Voters of Georgia - Minutes, reports, 1945-1948 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - League of Women Voters of Georgia - Extension committee, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - League of Women Voters of Georgia - Printed materials, 1944-1958 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - League of Women Voters of Georgia - Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Norman Raoul papers, 1900-1931, Subseries 1.13; Personal name.; Box 35
    Norman Raoul was born in New Brighton on Staten Island, New York on March 22, 1890. He was educated at Woodberry Forest School in Orange, Virginia, and the Culver Military Academy in Culver, Indiana. Between 1908 and 1910, he held positions with the Georgia Power Company and the Atlanta Clearing House. Norman worked for the Odorless Refrigerator Company in Chattanooga from 1910 until 1917, when he enlisted in the U.S. Army. During World War I, he served as an artillery officer with the 82nd Division of the American Expeditionary Force in France. Returning to Chattanooga after the war, he went to work for his father-in-law in the Chattanooga Implement and Manufacturing Company, serving first as treasurer and later vice-president. The depression of 1930 ended his twelve-year association with the company and in 1932 he became manager of the Post Exchange at Fort Oglethorpe, Georgia, near Chattanooga. Norman was a Mason and a member of the American Legion. He was married in 1915 to Frances Powell Sholar of Chattanooga. They were the parents of three children, Edward Sholar (1916-1919), Anne Elizabeth (b. 1921), and Norma Frances (b. 1929).
    Norman Raoul's letters are almost all to his mother, with a few to his father and sisters, Mary, Rosine, and Eleonore. They span the period 1900 to 1931, the bulk dating between 1900 and 1918. The subseries also contains one letter from Norman's wife Frances Sholar Raoul to her mother-in-law (1916). Several letters were written from the Woodberry Forest School that Norman attended from 1902 to 1905, and the Culver Military Academy in Culver, Indiana, which he attended from 1906 to 1908. These letters concern school activities, sporting events, and academic and disciplinary problems at Woodberry Forest that led to his withdrawal in February 1905. Letters from Atlanta and Chattanooga, where Norman settled in 1910 to work for his brother Gaston at the Odorless Refrigerator Company discuss work, marriage, children and perennial financial problems (1910-1913). Other letters, censored by military authorities, document Norman's service during World War I in the trenches and at the Saumur Artillery School in France (1918).
    Arranged by record type
    - Letters of Norman Raoul
    - 1900-1903 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - 1904 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - 1905, January-February (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - 1905, March-October (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - 1906, January-August (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - 1906, September-December (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - 1907, January-April (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - 1907, May-December (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - 1908, January-February (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - 1908, March-August (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - 1909-1910 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - 1911 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - 1912 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - 1915-1916 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - 1918 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Letter of Frances Sholar Raoul
    - 1916 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Photographs, circa 1850-1960, Series 2; Boxes 36-41; OP 3-6, 11
  Among the family photographs in Series 2 are portrait photographs of family members, snapshots of home life, travels and other activities, and additional photographs collected by the family. Boxes 36-38 contain photographs of the thirteen principal family members represented in Series 1 and of their immediate families; Box 39 contains photographs of other Raoul and Wadley relatives and miscellaneous subjects associated with the family; Box 40 contains portraits of unidentified individuals and groups and miscellaneous snapshots of persons and scenes; and Box 41 contains a collection of stereographs.
  Among the subjects documented by the photographs are turn-of-the-century residences in Seattle (Millis family snapshots), Tom Raoul's rustic life in Oracle, Arizona (1904-1906), Rosine Raoul's activities at Loomis Sanatorium (1911-1912), Eleonore Raoul's school days at Saint Timothy's (1906), the visit of William Jennings Bryan to Atlanta (1907), and the travels of the Raoul children in Europe and the Orient. Others depict the Raoul sons' business activities, including William Greene Raoul, Jr. with employees of the South Atlantic Car and Manufacturing Company in Waycross (1906), Tom Raoul and operations at the S. M. Inman and Company in Macon (1895-1896), and Gaston Raoul's refrigerator manufacturing concern in Chattanooga (stereographs). Photographs of the Peachtree Street and Great Hill Place houses are included, as are a number of photos of the Albemarle Park hotel and cottages in Asheville. An 1882 photograph shows the headquarters of the Central of Georgia Railway Company draped with mourning ribbon after the death of William M. Wadley. Atlanta photographer Columbus Washington Motes took a number of the photographs in this series.
  - William Greene Raoul, pre-1900 (4 cartes-de-visite, 11 cabinet photos) (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - William Greene Raoul, post-1900 (9 photos, 3 snapshots) (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - William Greene Raoul, and Mary Wadley Raoul (1 photo) (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Mary Wadley Raoul, ca. 1850-1895 (6 cartes-de-visite, 5 cabinet photos) (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Mary Wadley Raoul, 1900-ca. 1930 (9 photos, 4 snapshots) (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - William Greene Raoul, and Mary Wadley Raoul, children, ca. 1910 (1 photo) (Box 36, Folder 5a)
  - Sarah L. Wadley (8 photos including 1 carte-de-visite, 3 cabinet photos, and 1 snapshot) (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Mary Raoul Millis, ca. 1875-1910 (8 photos including 3 cabinet photos and 4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - John Millis (1 photo) (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Ralph Millis, 1895-1934 (8 photos including 2 cabinet photos and 1 snapshot) (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Walter Millis, 1901-ca. 1910 (7 photos) (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Janet Millis, ca. 1910 (1 photo) (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Millis children, 1900-1906 (4 photos including 1 cabinet photo) (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Millis family snapshots, 1901-1912 (48 snapshots) (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - William Greene Raoul, Jr., 1876-1901 (9 photos including 2 cartes-de-visite and 2 cabinet photos) (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - William Greene Raoul, Jr., 1906-1925 (16 photos including 1 cyanotype and 3 snapshots) (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Ruth Cunningham Raoul, ca. 1901 (2 photos) (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Gaston C. Raoul, ca. 1878-1930 (5 photos including 1 carte-de-visite and 3 cabinet photos) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Gaston C. Raoul family, 1910-1921 (14 photos including 7 snapshots) (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Wadley Raoul, ca. 1880-1897 (10 photos and 1 picture including 3 cabinet photos and 1 carte-de-visite) (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Thomas Wadley Raoul, 1900-1927 (26 photos including 21 snapshots) (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Wadley Raoul and family, 1914-1917 (15 photos including 3 snapshots) (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Wadley Raoul and family, 1920-1945 (22 photos including 3 snapshots) (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Rebecca Barnard Raoul and family, 1902-1954 (5 photos including 1 cyanotype and 4 snapshots) (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Agnes Raoul and family, 1884-1954 (9 photos including 3 cartes-de-visite and 3 cabinet photos) (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Rosine Raoul, 1888-1911 (11 photos including 2 cartes-de-visite and 3 cabinet photos) (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Rosine Raoul, 1909-1913 (photo album - mainly snapshots) (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Rosine Raoul at Loomis Sanatorium, 1911-1912 (45 photos - mainly snapshots) (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Rosine Raoul - miscellaneous (29 photos - mainly snapshots) (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Loring Raoul, ca. 1900-1918 (9 photos) (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Loring Raoul family, ca. 1910-1930 (9 photos) (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Eleonore Raoul and family, ca. 1889-1960 (46 photos including 4 cabinet photos and 24 snapshots) [Image 0548-001.tif] (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Eleonore Raoul at Saint Timothy's, 1906 (photo album) (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Harry L. Greene, Jr. and family, 1962-1967 (41 snapshots) (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Harry L. Greene, Jr. and family, undated (21 photos - mainly snapshots) (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Norman Raoul and family, ca. 1900-1960 (13 photos) (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - William Greene Raoul and daughters with William Jennings Bryan, ca. 1907 (2 photos) (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Raoul children - group portraits, ca. 1905-1930 (3 photos) (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Tom, Rebecca, and Agnes Raoul in Europe, 1903 (13 snapshots) (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Mary Raoul Millis and Rebecca Raoul in Japan, 1906 (2 cartes-de-visite, 26 snapshots) (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Tom and Rosine Raoul in Germany, 1909 (9 snapshots) (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Rebecca Everingham Wadley Noble (1 carte-de-visite and 2 cabinet photos) (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Gaston Turner Raoul (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Robert Giffin Raoul (1 photo) (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Yvonne Raoul (6 photos) (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Colcord Wadley (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - George Dole Wadley (2 photos including 1 cabinet photo) (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Henrietta Wadley (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - J. E. Wadley (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Loring Wadley, 1885 (1 cabinet photo) (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Rebecca B. Wadley, 1866-1890 (3 photos including 1 carte-de-visite and 1 cabinet photo) (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - William M. Wadley, 1850-ca. 1880 (10 photos including 3 cartes-de-visite and 1 cabinet photo) (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - William Oconius Wadley, 1901 (1 cabinet photo) (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Death mask of Napoleon (1 photo) (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Cuba and Mexico scenes, ca. 1887 (26 photos mounted on album pages) (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Albemarle Park, Asheville, N.C. (33 photos including album of 28 photos) (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Raoul mansion exterior and interior (17 photos, 1 set of negatives) [See also OP11] (Box 39, Folder 15a)
  - Peachtree Street Raoul mansion, interior and exterior (13 photos) (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous homes and buildings associated with Raoul family (6 photos) (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified individuals (3 tintypes, 7 cartes-de-visite) (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified individuals (6 cabinet photos) (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified individuals (11 photos) (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified individuals (12 photos, 1 silhouette) (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified groups (6 photos including 2 tintypes) (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified groups (11 photos) (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous persons (31 photos - mainly snapshots including 1 cabinet photo) (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous persons (28 photos mainly snapshots) (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous scenes (23 photos mainly snapshots) (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous scenes (31 photos mainly snapshots) (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous scenes (37 photos mainly snapshots) (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Scenes of Refrigerator Manufacturing Company, Chattanooga, Tennessee (16 stereographs) (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - Refrigerator models (24 stereographs) (Box 41, Folder 3-5)
  - Refrigerator models (6 stereographs, 1 pictorial envelope, 1 booklet) (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Savannah, Georgia scenes (3 stereographs) (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Paris views (83 stereographs) (Box 41, Folder 8-11)
  - Photo albums
  - Rose Bank" (1905), "Crow's Nest" (1905), Canon del Oro (1906), Reading Room Oracle (1905), unidentified photos from a [family trip out west?], 1905, 1906, family shot (1909) (Box 41a, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified and undated [continuation of album 1?] (Box 41a, Folder 2)
  - Oversized photographs
  - Loring Raoul, ca. 1902-1904 (Box OP3)
  - Raoul sons, 1890 (Box OP4)
  - Great Hill Place, Bolingbroke, Georgia (Box OP5)
  - Unidentified groups (Box OP6)
  - Raoul mansion: Interior (Box OP11)
- Financial and legal papers, 1890-1970, Boxes 42-45; OBV 1
  Raoul family financial and legal papers include records relating to the estates of W. G. Raoul and Mary Wadley Raoul, Eleonore Raoul's financial records, and a few miscellaneous materials.
  The W. G. Raoul Estate papers are primarily real estate records relating to a group of Atlanta lots owned by Raoul on Piedmont Avenue between 11th and 14th Streets. These documents include abstracts of titles, warranty deeds, plats, and tax and improvement records (1890-1922). A folder relating to the Raoul Heirs, Inc., a corporation set up to administer the estate, contains stock certificates and correspondence between the heirs concerning taxes and the sale of stocks and property. The Mary Wadley Raoul Estate papers (boxes 43-44) include correspondence, reports, tax records, investment statements, and real estate records (1890-1953). Most of the real estate records relate to Mary W. Raoul's property holdings in Bibb County and the western part of Fulton County along Gordon Road. These records include agreements, contracts, deeds, plats, tax records, titles, and correspondence about repairs, rentals, and sales. Other real estate records relate to the Peachtree Street house and include agreements, leases, and correspondence concerning insurance, maintenance, rental, and the sale of the property to the American Red Cross in 1941. Mary Wadley Raoul's will (1936) is included as are files for the trust funds set up for her sons Tom and Norman. Much of the correspondence in these estate papers is between the Raoul children, particularly Gaston, as administrator of the Raoul Heirs, Inc., and Eleonore as executrix of the Mary Wadley Raoul Estate.
  Records of Eleonore Raoul include statements of investments, tax returns, and miscellaneous financial and legal papers (1927-1970). Among the latter are items relating to her property in Highlands, North Carolina and a portion of her 1970 will.
  Miscellaneous materials in this series concern the purchase of Great Hill Place (William M. Wadley Estate) by Mary Wadley Raoul (1921) and the construction on Lullwater Road of a home designed by architect W. T. Downing (1914).
  - W. G. Raoul estate papers and miscellaneous
  - W. G. Raoul Estate - Real estate records for property on Piedmont Avenue, 1890-1946 (Box 42, Folder 1-8)
  - W. G. Raoul Estate - Property tax receipts, 1913-1920 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - W. G. Raoul Estate - Raoul Heirs, Inc., 1918-1946 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - William M. Wadley Estate - miscellaneous, 1921-1923 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Lullwater Road home (Box 42, Folder 12-13)
  - Miscellaneous family legal papers, 1962-1967 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - William Greene Raoul Lists of assets and debits; general outline of will (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Mary W. Raoul estate papers
  - Ledger, 1936-1948 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Will, 1936 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Wadley Raoul Trust Fund, 1929-1953 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Norman Raoul Trust Fund, 1931-1946 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Bibb County property, 1923-1941 (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
  - Fulton County properties, 1890-1948 (Box 43, Folder 7-9)
  - Peachtree Street property, 1937-1941 (Box 43, Folder 10-11)
  - General records, 1936-1951 (Box 44, Folder 1-4)
  - Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Tax records, 1936-1942 (Box 44, Folder 6-7)
  - Statements, 1940-1941 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Raoul Estates, Inc. - statements, 1940-1946 (Box 44, Folder 9-14)
  - Eleonore Raoul records
  - Ledger, 1929-1932 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Investment statements, 1927-1933 (Box 45, Folder 2-8)
  - Tax returns, 1934-1945 (Box 45, Folder 9-13)
  - Miscellaneous financial records, 1927-1950 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous legal records, 1924-1970 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Oversized volume
  - Ledger of Mary Wadley Raoul, 1932-1936 (Box OBV 1)
- Miscellaneous, 1881-1982, Series 4; Box 46; OP 7-10
  Miscellaneous items in Series 4 include materials relating to the Raoul family/genealogy, the Raoul mansion, and writings about the Raoul family. Of particular interest in the Raoul family/genealogy material is a journal spanning nearly twenty years (1881-1899) containing entries written by each of the Raouls and documenting their lives in Savannah (1881-1886), New Brighton, New York (1889-1892), and Atlanta (1894-1899). Topics include the education, illnesses, and activities of the children, visits from relatives and friends, vacations and other travels. The births of the younger children are recorded, as well as the deaths of William Wadley, Edward Raoul, and Loring Wadley. Included in the journal are cablegrams, obituaries, other clippings, poems, and stories by the children.
  Materials relating to the Raoul mansion include printed materials relating to the Mansion, blueprints of Raoul properties, a 1926 plat of the Druid Hills subdivision, and the original 1891 plan for landscaping the family's Peachtree Street house by architect Bradford Gilbert is also included.
  Writings about the Raoul family include a photocopy of Mary Raoul Millis's The Family of Raoul: A Memoir (1943), as well as a typescript of her unfinished autobiography, written about 1953. The autobiography covers ca. 1870-1910, and breaks off at the point of her involvement with the Socialist Party. Subjects covered by the clippings include weddings and deaths, developments in Asheville, John Millis's army assignments, activities of the Millis children, and the Peachtree Street and Great Hill Place houses.
  - Miscellaneous, 1881-1982, Subseries 4.1; Box 46; OP 7-10
    - Genealogy, Subseries 4.1a
      - Raoul family journal, 1881-1899 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Gaston Cesar Raoul de Champmanoir: Baptismal record: Holograph copy, December 23, 1873 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Genealogy part 2, Subseries 4.1b
      - Theus and Raoul de Champmanoir families: Genealogical information (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence Jane Raoul Bingham/ Emily L. Wenzel; William Gaston Raoul to Sam, July 26 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Memorabilia - general, ca. 1886-1897 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Fiction, 1973-2006, Subseries 2.1; Boxes 15-45; OP1-5
    This subseries contains all materials related to the writing and preparation for publication of each of Rushdie's novels or short stories, from 1973-2006. All of his published works, including Grimus, Midnight's Children, Shame, The Satanic Verses, Haroun and the Sea of Stories, East West, The Moor's Last Sigh, The Ground Beneath Her Feet, Fury, and Shalimar the Clown are represented. Frequently, the subseries frequently contains multiple typescript versions of a novel, many of which are heavily annotated and corrected in Rushdie's hand. At times, typescript versions differ significantly from the published text, with characters and scenes that are excised from the final version; often, Rushdie's drafts contain many versions of a single page, giving the researcher significant insight into his creative process that is supplemented by the large body of manuscript and typescript notes related to the composition of each work. Additionally, the series contains unpublished fiction, including The Antagonist, The Avatar, Madame Rama, and The Book of the Peer, as well as fragments of additional novels or stories or the title pages for planned novels. The arrangement of the material within each work roughly follows the creative process from early manuscript or typescript drafts through to galley and page proofs.
    Additional drafts and notes for East, West, The Moor's Last Sigh, The Ground Beneath Her Feet, and various short stories can be found in the digital files. A detailed list of the files is available by accessing the searchable database and emulated environment on the researcher workstation in the Manuscript, Archives, and Rare Book Library (MARBL) reading room.
    Novels are arranged in chronological order by date of publication, followed by short stories and unpublished works arranged alphabetically.
    Restrictions on Access
    Selected notes and unpublished writings are restricted. Access to digital files is only available in the Manuscript, Archives, and Rare Book Library (MARBL).
    - Published Works
    - Grimus (1975)
Index of Selected Correspondents
Names of prominent local citizens, Georgia business and political leaders, some nationally prominent figures, and some schools and regional business concerns, are indexed here. Correspondence throughout Series 1; photographs of individuals in Series 2 and some special materials in Series 3 and 4 are covered by this index.
This is an index to selected correspondents, corporate names and photographic subjects, rather than a comprehensive index. Letters to or from and photographs of the thirteen family members prominently represented in Series 1 have not been individually indexed here.
Index reference to correspondence is to series number, box number, folder number, and number of items. For example, the notation "1 - 31:3 (2)" refers to Series 1, box 31, folder 3, two items. Series numbers have not been repeated when one individual is represented by multiple index entries from the same series. For example, "1 - 2:1 (1); 2:2 (1); 17:10 (1)" describes items all found in Series 1. Index reference to corporate name is to series and subseries number only; researchers should refer to subseries notes and inventories for more detailed information.
Alexander, Edwin Porter, 1835-1910 Series 1 - 2:1 (2); 2:5 (1)
Allen, William Frederick, 1846-1915 Series 1 - 2:4 (2)
Atlantic and Birmingham Railway Company SEE Series 1.1
Bacon, Augustus Octavius, 1839-1914 Series 1 - 2:1 (1); 2:2 (1); 17:10 (1)